Senpai?
She doesn't stay late enough
to eat dinner in the office often...
March on, Meowtaro!
Meow, meow, meow! Meow, meow, meow!
She's singing her heart out!
She noticed me?
March on, Meowtaro!
She kept singing?!
Meow, meow, meow!
And she wants me to join in?!
Good job, Shinozaki-san!
That was nicely done.
What a cute abuse of authority.
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#11 Can I Give You a Big Hug?
What should I drink?
Working late on your entry? Good for you.
Here, for you.
Thank... you...
Why not just throw together something simple?
Well, I'm headed home. See you around!
Can't just... throw something together.
Need to help the director aim higher...
Good morning.
What's wrong, everyone?
I should be the one asking you that!
The deadline for the competition
is soon. He might be overdoing it...
Oh, I'm totally fine!
Is what I say but...
I'm freaking out on the inside!
The pressure of competing directly
with someone at work for the first time,
the responsibility of needing
to keep our manager with us...
It's so much I could use some rehab,
but I can't tell Senpai that!
See...? I'm fine...
Now, let's get to work...
Shinozaki-san.
Specially made by your senpai,
it's the kanji for "person."
Please, eat up.
Wh-Why?
You're worried about your proposal for
the competition being perfect, aren't you?
Please don't be afraid to fail.
It doesn't matter if it goes smoothly.
I'd even say this contest is about
accepting that kind of thing.
Just swing as hard as you can!
And it's just accepted I'll miss?
Thank you.
Yep!
Product Development
Group 1
Magnificent!
The concept, the targeting...
Both are clearly laid out and easy to grasp.
Thank you.
All you need now is an image to
illustrate the complete project
The Ultimate Meowtaro
and it'll be an even easier sell.
An illustration...
Yeah. Even a simple one would be fine.
You're almost there.
Don't worry, Kurusu. You can do this!
Right...
Senpai helped me calm down some.
Okay, let's do this...
Oh, sorry!
Hey, Senpai...
You know that girl, Kurusu,
in Development Group 1?
Sure, I do.
She's taking on the new hire contest like me,
and I think she's feeling
just as much pressure.
If you see her, I'd appreciate it if you
could try and help her feel better...
Sorry, I know I shouldn't be
asking you to do this!
But I think she'd be too on-guard around me.
Not to mention, I may be being
nosy for no good reason.
Understood.
I'll keep that in mind.
I appreciate it.
Still working?
You're from Development Group 2...
I'm Katase Shiori.
Do you always stay this late?
That's none of your business.
There are some things a third party
might have a clearer view on, though.
Group 2 is the enemy.
I have nothing to say to you.
Do you mind if I sit with you?
Listen to me!
That pouch...
It was released for Meowtaro's
20th anniversary, wasn't it?
You recognize it?!
I have one, too.
There was another one
that came out with a ribbon...
I have that one, too!
Meowtaro's head was rounder
back then, with smaller eyes,
and you could tell the art was more
analog, but that made it cuter...
A-And well...
Even though this is the Meowtaro company...
I don't get many chances to talk about him...
Please, have a seat.
Thank you.
If you like Meowtaro that much,
you must be really motivated
for the rookie competition, too.
Katase-san...
Katase-san, is there anything
you have trouble with at work?
A whole lot of things!
Laying out diagrams and adjusting text...
Could you look at this?
Does it remind you of any Taro in particular?
That's a very leading question!
I'm no good at art...
I've managed to keep that
a secret the past year.
But I can't anymore...
I don't want to disappoint her.
I've tried so many times...
but I just can't get better.
I want to do a good job, Katase-san!
How can I deliver for her?
What do I do?
Maybe you should just...
tell her that you can't do it.
But if I do that...
Admitting when you can't do
something is part of your job.
Besides...
No one's going to ridicule you
for having tried your best.
Okay... I'll try and tell her.
Director.
I've... updated my proposal.
Please, look...
Sure. Knowing you, Kurusu,
I'm sure it's evolved a fair...
The Ultimate Meowtaro
This art...
I'm... so sorry.
I tried, but... it was...
the best I could do...
You said I would be able
to do it... but I failed!
No, you didn't...
You didn't fail, Kurusu.
I should be the one to apologize.
I thought I was encouraging you,
but I was just pouring on more pressure.
Please, forgive me, Kurusu.
Director...
Hanaoka-san, could you help
with Kurusu's proposal?
Sure.
Sorry about this...
It's no problem at all.
There's a couple of days left
before the deadline!
We're going to support Kurusu
as much as we can in that time!
Yeah!
Development Group 1 is really motivated.
Yeah.
What a relief...
He's under a lot of pressure himself, but he's
still nice enough to worry about others...
Did I do something funny?
Not at all. I'm just impressed
with you, Shinozaki-san.
Wh-What for, Senpai?
March on, Meowtaro!
Meow, meow, meow!
My Tiny Meowtaro.
You sure that's the title?
It's finally the day of the competition.
Everything ready, Shinozaki-san?
Yep! All set.
You're absolutely sure you're ready?
I am really sure that I'm all set!
I have to say...
I didn't expect you to make
a Meowtaro costume...
Are you a goddess, Hayakawa-san?!
Not really, no.
Compared to my usual, cosplay it was
pretty simple, so it's not like...
Your usual what?
Uh, er, nothing! Never mind!
Oh, my.
Thank you for all your help, Senpai.
It's all right.
Senpai, is it just me, or are you
more nervous than I am?
My direct subordinate is entering his
biggest moment of the entire year!
Of course I am!
I am so full of butterflies right now...
Senpai, calm down. It'll be okay.
Is there anything else I can do?
Kurusu-san.
During the presentations... I go on before you.
Hrmmm
It kind of ended up feeling like
a showdown, didn't it?
Let's both do our best.
Um...
Thank you.
Katase-san mentioned...
you were worried about me.
I'm... grateful.
Sure.
But...
We're going to win.
Win, and take your manager.
I don't intend on losing, either.
We're going to win, and keep our manager!
Looking forward to your presentation.
Okay! Let's do this!
This talk about losing
or keeping the manager...
What's that all about?
Uh, well... the truth is...
The truth is...?
Excuse me?!
Report! Stay in contact! Consult!
Report
Stay in contact
Consult
You didn't do any one of those!
Sorry...
I knew about it.
Me, too.
So I'm the only one who didn't?!
Maybe we can still negotiate...
But she's probably already into her proposal...
What do we do?!
Senpai.
Specially made by your kouhai,
it's the kanji for "person."
I really am sorry that
I didn't tell you sooner.
But I've been under your guidance
for a whole year now.
I know I won't lose.
Gosh... if you put it like that...
I won't be able to say anything back.
Shinozaki-san is guaranteed to win
the most valuable rookie award!
Right!
You just need spirit! Let's all huddle up!
Okay!
Okay...
Development Group 2, fight!
Yeah!
Group 1
Team Kurusu
That was the presentation from
Kurusu's team with Development Group 1.
Next will be Shinozaki's team
from Development Group 2.
I know I said he was guaranteed
to win most valuable rookie...
but I'm still worried.
Our proposal involves coming up
with new ways to share "fun."
"Taking what I enjoy today, and letting
other people enjoy it tomorrow."
And in order to make that possible...
Group 2
Team Shinozaki
we will need Meowtaro, the super friend!
Super friend?
Friends...
Friends, huh?
Strategy meeting
Friends
Yes.
It's something that came to mind
when we were with the preschool class.
There're unlimited ways to have fun...
What if there was someone who existed
to help people share that fun?
What if they had that kind of friend?
I see...
I was hoping to ask you all about
what you heard about from the kids.
There was one who liked skateboarding.
I remember one who was good with magic tricks.
Nice!
This friend could recommend
those kinds of things,
and it'll create fondness and
identification almost instantly!
Wow!
Look at him go on that skateboard.
I wanna try that.
Looks like fun!
Things are working out
just like Shinozaki-san planned.
Is that Shinozaki-kun inside the suit?
Oh, no! I think I might fall for him!
It's working out as planned,
but maybe he's overdoing it.
Besides, Meowtaro is Meowtaro. There's not
supposed to be anyone "in the suit."
Wow!
Cute!
That was amazing!
You're amazing, Meowtaro.
Aren't they all getting a little
touchy with that costume?
So cute!
You're grown adults. You should realize
there's someone inside that suit!
Completely ignoring what she
was thinking minutes ago
But...
That was a wonderful finish
for your first year.
That was Team Shinozaki from Development Group 2.
Good work.
Your presentation was amazing!
I'm sure you'll win
the most valuable rookie award!
It looks like Hayakawa-san
went back to her seat already.
And, well... I know you might be
feeling tired right now, but...
I was hoping I could ask for something.
Can I give you a big hug, too?
I-It's just that everyone else was doing it,
and I was wondering what it was like!
Why are you running?!
You let everyone else touch you lots!
Thank you so much!
Sorry I had to duck out like that...
There was an urgent data correction
I had to take care of.
Shinozaki-san?!
Then, who's...
This Meowtaro?
It's me!
Wha—
Go and give her a big hug!
Cut it out!
Come on, they're announcing the winner!
Let's get back to the hall!
No hug, then?
Stop, Manager!
Results Announcement
The time has come. I will now be announcing
the results of the new hire competition.
Who the heck is gonna win?
That Meowtaro was Akina-san?
Hey there!
Now, before the prizes are presented,
a few words from the president.
Most Valuable New Hire Award
Before we announce
the most valuable rookie award,
Excellence Award Team 1
Excellence Award Team 2
I'd like to award the two teams
receiving the awards for excellence.
The first will be going to...
Shinozaki's team with Development Group 2!
The other...
Kurusu's team with Development Group 1!
Most Valuable New Hire Award
Excellence Award
Development Group 2
Team Shinozaki
Excellence Award
Development Group 1
Team Kurusu
These are our excellence
award winners! Congratulations!
I guess I ended up tying with Kurusu-san.
The Okinawan resort...
What are you talking about?
You might not have won
the most promising rookie,
but the excellence award is great, too!
You should be happy!
You're right!
An award of excellence, eh?
I'm so sorry...
Whatever for?
Everyone helped me... but I
couldn't win most valuable new hire...
No one's upset with you for that.
Congratulations on your award, Kurusu.
But you won't get their manager now...
You said you needed him for your ambitions...
I was so focused on
the competition I forgot about that!
You forgot?!
Yeah.
Besides...
You're a-meow-zing,
Dev Group 1 Team Kurusu
Seeing everyone work so hard
made me realize something.
All I need to strive for greater heights...
are my valuable subordinates.
Director...
Here's to further working together, Kurusu.
Right!
And now, at long last, we will be announcing
the most valuable rookie award!
Most Valuable New Hire Award
Excellence Award
Development Group 2
Team Shinozaki
Excellence Award
Development Group 1
Team Kurusu
Out of all the submissions, the one selected
for the most prestigious prize is...
Yamagishi's team from Public Relations!
No way... Me?
Yay!
Where did you get the idea
for your proposal from?
Nowhere in particular...
It's all thanks to my daily guidance!
He was the least motivated, and yet...!
This is... really frustrating.
And that concludes the annual
new hire competition.
Shinozaki-san, you did a great job!
There's a big wrap party to celebrate, too.
It'll be my victory party!
No, it won't be.
Right?!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar
Work drags so much in the afternoon...
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Just the excellence one.
It ain't like that at all!
Holler at you later!
Forget... what you heard.
Not gonna happen that fast.
Don't try the physical approach.
What's the big deal anyway?
It's... embarrassing.
I don't see how.
We don't have any sort of obvious accent
where I'm from, so I'm kinda jealous.
Jealous...?
Yeah, it's kinda cool.
Man, lunch is gonna end
if we don't wrap up here.
H-Hey...
Thank you kindly.
Thank me whatly?